{
  "shortDescription": "Test your knowledge of Chevrolet with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What year was Chevy founded?",
      "answers": ["1911", "1920", "1935"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's sports car?",
      "answers": ["Camaro", "Malibu", "Impala"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Where is Chevy headquartered?",
      "answers": ["LA", "Detroit", "NYC"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who founded Chevy?",
      "answers": ["Henry", "Louis", "David"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's pickup?",
      "answers": ["Ranger", "Ram", "Silverado"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a Chevy SUV?",
      "answers": ["Civic", "Tahoe", "Fit"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's slogan?",
      "answers": ["Like a Rock", "Zoom-Zoom", "Let's Go"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Chevy is a hybrid?",
      "answers": ["Volt", "Taurus", "Fiesta"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's electric car?",
      "answers": ["Model 3", "Leaf", "Bolt"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a Chevy compact?",
      "answers": ["Cruze", "Explorer", "Expedition"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What year was Camaro launched?",
      "answers": ["1964", "1966", "1970"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Chevy is full-size?",
      "answers": ["Edge", "Fiesta", "Suburban"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is Chevy's crossover?",
      "answers": ["Edge", "Fusion", "Equinox"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's luxury brand?",
      "answers": ["Cadillac", "Lexus", "Lincoln"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's midsize?",
      "answers": ["Malibu", "Focus", "Fiesta"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Chevy has AWD?",
      "answers": ["Fiesta", "Trax", "Explorer"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's subcompact?",
      "answers": ["Trax", "Edge", "Escape"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which Chevy has Turbo?",
      "answers": ["Volt", "Cruze", "Focus"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is a Chevy hatchback?",
      "answers": ["Escape", "Cruze", "F-150"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Chevy's performance line?",
      "answers": ["RS", "ST", "SS"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    }
  ]
}
